( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
Black Street
Infamous.
People say
the world's most vicious criminals live here.
Murder, arson,
every evil imaginable.
Or rather,
the Black Street of the past
used to be like that.
Until a group of homeless
masters seeking seclusion
discovered this place,
wiped out those villains,
and took over their nest.
Outsiders still avoid Black Street.
So these people play along,
putting on vicious faces
just for some peace and quiet.
No one bothers anyone.
As for me,
my name is Su Yang.
They call me
Madman.
Half a spoon of salt fell into the pot.
That dream is still bothering you.
Tormenting me, more like.
What did you just say?
I said...
Never mind.
So you're leaving Black Street to...?
To verify something.
Even if the verification proves
the dream is real,
what can you do about it?
Obviously...
What is that?
I...
I have to record this!
Look, look!
I got it on camera, look!
Hurry, record it!
Quick, take a picture!
See the Celestial Palace in the sky?
Look, look!
Look, there are Immortals!
Can we cultivate immortality now?
Is this for real?
Hurry, record it!
Who are you playing the good student for?
Think you can get close to Chu Lingling?
Come on, record this clearly!
Come on!
I've never seen anything like this.
Am I seeing this right?
Today I become an Immortal,
treading upon the Ninth Heaven,
summoning lightning from all sides!
Who told you to stand up?
Get back down!
The green lamp, ever by my side.
A giant axe splits the mountain.
The path to immortality stretches far.
Descending into the mortal world.
Chenxiang splits the mountain!
Starting today,
no one can bully me.
No one at all.
A thousand years ago,
the Celestial Realm faced the Great Tribulation of Inner Demons.
Countless Immortals fell into madness
and slaughtered each other,
causing the Celestial Realm to collapse.
Great Tribulation of Inner Demons.
Calamity born of the heart.
Tribulation, my ass.
If we die, we die together.
The Immortals lost much of their power,
losing control over the mortal world.
To survive this, the Immortal Emperor
expended his essence
to set up eight sealing gates,
sealing all Immortals within.
He then sent word to all Immortals:
In a millennium, when inner demons fade,
only a mortal bearing the Celestial Seed,
opening the 8 Immortal-Sealing Gates,
can the Celestial Realm regain control.
Do you believe that in this world,
Immortals really speak through dreams?
I do.
No.
You don't.
What are you trying to say?
I often have this dream.
Coincidentally,
the scene in the dream
and this place
are identical.
A robber
killed a psychiatrist,
and hid the body
inside the bathroom.
Who the hell are you?
Who I am doesn't matter.
It's just that
in ten more seconds,
this robber
will be hit by a car and killed.
If
you aren't killed,
then that proves
it was all just a dream.
You...
Listen.
Three.
Two.
One.
Looks like
this isn't a dream.
So that bizarre, fantastical world
will eventually arrive.
I can't wait.
What happened?
That's a serious crash!
This guy's gotta be dead, right?
Take a break.
Thanks.
So,
in your scenario,
what's the Immortals' true purpose?
Ancient Immortals are about to descend,
sowing Celestial Seeds among mortals.
Everyone gets a chance at immortality.
A heaven-sent temptation
slowly unfolds around Su Yang.
But
the Celestial Realm controls mortals via blessings.
As the Chosen One, Su Yang,
how is he going to break through?
Indeed.
How will he break through?
First,
he needs to find that gate,
a gate that can change the world.
Unload the cargo.
Six of them,
all alive and kicking.
What's going on?
So it's here.
Exactly like in my dream.
But many of the details
I can't remember clearly.
If you hadn't led the way,
I'd never have found it.
Thanks,
big bro.
Brother,
State your business.
I live on Black Street.
They all like to call me
Madman.
Bro, bro, bro!
He says he's the Madman.
What are you panicking for?
You believe he's the Madman just like that?
Call the boss.
Have him send a photo of Madman. Go!
Okay, okay, okay.
Brother,
though I've long admired the Madman,
I've never actually met him.
If someone were impersonating him
and ruining his reputation,
I think
that wouldn't be right either.
So could you prove your identity?
How do I prove it?
Well then,
let me show you some madness.
Nobody move!
Get back here.
Is that proof enough?
Even if you might not be the Madman,
still,
we still can't afford to mess with you.
Suit yourself.
Please, go right ahead.
Bro, bro!
He really is the Madman.
We brothers were in the wrong.
We offended you.
You...
I need quiet.
I get it.
Brothers, let's go!
It really is just like in my dream.
In my dreams,
this gate appears most often.
So those seemingly prophetic dreams
all came from you?
Damn it.
It's
happening again.
Push open this gate
to become an Immortal,
to live forever,
to be eternal through the ages.
So this is
why you kept weaving dreams
to lure me here?
Becoming an Immortal
seems like
a pretty good path.
I can almost feel your
joy
Becoming an Immortal.
Eternal life.
Do you know
how much I hate having
strange dreams while I sleep?
Even opening the gate
depends on my mood.
Not having you pester me day and night.
Finding you
has wasted so much of my time.
So you do bleed.
An Immortal
can feel pain too.
The other seven Immortal Gates have risen.
If the main gate doesn't rise soon,
calamity will descend.
You're playing with fire.
Would you ignore the future?
If you could really foresee the future,
you definitely wouldn't have chosen me.
Because in this life,
what I hate most
is being threatened.
Possession,
body-snatching,
or a curse?
If destroying you were easy,
that'd be too boring.
This is just right.
We can take our time.
Hurry up!
He's back! He's back!
The monkey isn't untied yet.
Forget the damn monkey!
Just run!
Move!